[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "I'm in good shape.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "in", "good", "shape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What is your view of this debate right now and what should be done?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "this", "debate", "right", "now", "and", "what", "should", "be", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Does it depress you that even following a massacre as we saw at Sandy Hook School, there are still so many Americans who want no change at all?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "depress", "you", "that", "even", "following", "a", "massacre", "as", "we", "saw", "at", "Sandy", "Hook", "School", ",", "there", "are", "still", "so", "many", "Americans", "who", "want", "no", "change", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNPS", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, you know, they're not evil people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "evil", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sandy Hook School"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "The NRA you're talking about?", "question_tokens": ["The", "NRA", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Yes, I'm talking about the NRA.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "talking", "about", "the", "NRA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Why are politicians so cowed by the NRA?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "politicians", "so", "cowed", "by", "the", "NRA", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Because they marshal money for the opponents, and they have been successful in defeating candidates.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "they", "marshal", "money", "for", "the", "opponents", ",", "and", "they", "have", "been", "successful", "in", "defeating", "candidates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Where does it need to get to quite quickly, do you think, to maybe get back on its feet properly?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "it", "need", "to", "get", "to", "quite", "quickly", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "maybe", "get", "back", "on", "its", "feet", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, I believe that we're not doing enough to deal with the national debt.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "we", "'re", "not", "doing", "enough", "to", "deal", "with", "the", "national", "debt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Why were you so animated?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "so", "animated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Well, firstly, I want to say this: I don't think he's anti-Semitic.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "firstly", ",", "I", "want", "to", "say", "this", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "'s", "anti-Semitic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 147, "question": "So why would we want to jettison -- which is really the way I feel he's acting -- the only democratic state in that area that we can rely on, Israel, in exchange for having the sheikhs and the kings and the presidents in Egypt and Lebanon and Syria and Iraq toasting with orange juice Hagel's appointment?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "would", "we", "want", "to", "jettison", "--", "which", "is", "really", "the", "way", "I", "feel", "he", "'s", "acting", "--", "the", "only", "democratic", "state", "in", "that", "area", "that", "we", "can", "rely", "on", ",", "Israel", ",", "in", "exchange", "for", "having", "the", "sheikhs", "and", "the", "kings", "and", "the", "presidents", "in", "Egypt", "and", "Lebanon", "and", "Syria", "and", "Iraq", "toasting", "with", "orange", "juice", "Hagel", "'s", "appointment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "In terms of the Israel/Palestine situation, I mean, do you think that any kind of lasting peace settlement can be achieved without --", "answer_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "Israel/Palestine", "situation", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "any", "kind", "of", "lasting", "peace", "settlement", "can", "be", "achieved", "without", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hagel"], "LOCATION": ["Israel", "Egypt", "Lebanon", "Syria", "Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "You want me to tell me the truth or do you want me to stroke you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "me", "to", "tell", "me", "the", "truth", "or", "do", "you", "want", "me", "to", "stroke", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Can only they change it or do the Israelis have to also give a little bit?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "only", "they", "change", "it", "or", "do", "the", "Israelis", "have", "to", "also", "give", "a", "little", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Of course, the Israelis --", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "the", "Israelis", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "When you see it now, is it as bad as it's ever been, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "it", "now", ",", "is", "it", "as", "bad", "as", "it", "'s", "ever", "been", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Worse.", "answer_tokens": ["Worse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hillary"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Could we be facing our first female president?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "we", "be", "facing", "our", "first", "female", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I am for Hillary.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "for", "Hillary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Bill Clinton would still be president, wouldn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Bill", "Clinton", "would", "still", "be", "president", ",", "would", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Well, I am for term limits, but I'm for three terms.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "am", "for", "term", "limits", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "for", "three", "terms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine Quinn"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Who would be the next mayor of New York?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", "the", "next", "mayor", "of", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Well, I am for Christine Quinn, but it's a wide open race.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "am", "for", "Christine", "Quinn", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "a", "wide", "open", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Pretty tough act to follow, isn't he, Michael Bloomberg?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "tough", "act", "to", "follow", ",", "is", "n't", "he", ",", "Michael", "Bloomberg", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Very, very tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", ",", "very", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Bloomberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "How am I doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "am", "I", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Not too well.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "too", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What do you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "It's on a subway stop, too.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "on", "a", "subway", "stop", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Manhattan"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What was the thinking behind that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "thinking", "behind", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "OCH: It is the only operating cemetery in Manhattan.", "answer_tokens": ["OCH", ":", "It", "is", "the", "only", "operating", "cemetery", "in", "Manhattan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "When you look at your own grave, which is something that very, very people ever do, Mr. Mayor, what do you think when you look at it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "your", "own", "grave", ",", "which", "is", "something", "that", "very", ",", "very", "people", "ever", "do", ",", "Mr.", "Mayor", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "when", "you", "look", "at", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Well, I want to tell you, I -- I'm secular but I believe in God.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "want", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "--", "I", "'m", "secular", "but", "I", "believe", "in", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Is that what it says?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "it", "says", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What has been your biggest failure, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "your", "biggest", "failure", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "I'll tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "That was in Harlem, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "was", "in", "Harlem", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Yes, it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harlem"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "As a kind of rookie myself in the world of Super Bowls, why is this one going to be special, as the commissioner seems to suggest?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "kind", "of", "rookie", "myself", "in", "the", "world", "of", "Super", "Bowls", ",", "why", "is", "this", "one", "going", "to", "be", "special", ",", "as", "the", "commissioner", "seems", "to", "suggest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "This is a great Super Bowl.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "great", "Super", "Bowl", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Super Bowls"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What are the big issues surrounding the Super Bowl that you think America will be talking about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "big", "issues", "surrounding", "the", "Super", "Bowl", "that", "you", "think", "America", "will", "be", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "What else do I need to really be an American watching the Super Bowl on Sunday?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "do", "I", "need", "to", "really", "be", "an", "American", "watching", "the", "Super", "Bowl", "on", "Sunday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "The beer is very important.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "beer", "is", "very", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "What's going to be in the Piers Super Bowl celebration here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "in", "the", "Piers", "Super", "Bowl", "celebration", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I -- well, guacamole reminds me of mushy peas, which we have in chips in England, so maybe I'm a guacamole kind of guy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "well", ",", "guacamole", "reminds", "me", "of", "mushy", "peas", ",", "which", "we", "have", "in", "chips", "in", "England", ",", "so", "maybe", "I", "'m", "a", "guacamole", "kind", "of", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Pat, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Pat", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I'm fine, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "fine", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Where do you put this one?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "put", "this", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "'BRIEN: Well, the Super Bowl in America is -- should be a national holiday.", "answer_tokens": ["'BRIEN", ":", "Well", ",", "the", "Super", "Bowl", "in", "America", "is", "--", "should", "be", "a", "national", "holiday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Well, the one where they all have to wear helmets and padding, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "one", "where", "they", "all", "have", "to", "wear", "helmets", "and", "padding", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What is really going on between these two?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "really", "going", "on", "between", "these", "two", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "I think you're exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "But where are you seeing this one go?", "question_tokens": ["But", "where", "are", "you", "seeing", "this", "one", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, I used to like the 49ers a lot until I got here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "used", "to", "like", "the", "49ers", "a", "lot", "until", "I", "got", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Or is it really time that the sport got to grips with this and did something about it?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "really", "time", "that", "the", "sport", "got", "to", "grips", "with", "this", "and", "did", "something", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "No, I mean, the -- yes, good question.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "--", "yes", ",", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "If you were running it, would you bring in any new regulations to try to limit the impacts?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "running", "it", ",", "would", "you", "bring", "in", "any", "new", "regulations", "to", "try", "to", "limit", "the", "impacts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "There's only so much you can do.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "only", "so", "much", "you", "can", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Tell me what you were thinking as it began to fall apart?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "what", "you", "were", "thinking", "as", "it", "began", "to", "fall", "apart", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "It -- I didn't feel anything, which is actually a lot worse because then I had this like blank look on my face.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "feel", "anything", ",", "which", "is", "actually", "a", "lot", "worse", "because", "then", "I", "had", "this", "like", "blank", "look", "on", "my", "face", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Is it actually ripping?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "actually", "ripping", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "No, it's a tiered dress, which I didn't understand until I was like, why can I see my thighs.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "tiered", "dress", ",", "which", "I", "did", "n't", "understand", "until", "I", "was", "like", ",", "why", "can", "I", "see", "my", "thighs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "When you were a little youngster, what was the dream for you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "a", "little", "youngster", ",", "what", "was", "the", "dream", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I had a million dreams.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "a", "million", "dreams", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Louisville", "Kentucky"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "But tell me about your upbringing, your family, and what they make of all this?", "question_tokens": ["But", "tell", "me", "about", "your", "upbringing", ",", "your", "family", ",", "and", "what", "they", "make", "of", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I grew up in Louisville, Kentucky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "grew", "up", "in", "Louisville", ",", "Kentucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "How do they feel now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "they", "feel", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Now they're very relieved.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "they", "'re", "very", "relieved", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "What does she have, Jennifer, that takes it to that kind of level?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "have", ",", "Jennifer", ",", "that", "takes", "it", "to", "that", "kind", "of", "level", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I think there's a soulfulness that's immediately there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "soulfulness", "that", "'s", "immediately", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "How many seconds did it take to say yes to that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "seconds", "did", "it", "take", "to", "say", "yes", "to", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "About half a second.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "half", "a", "second", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "My God, this doesn't get any better?", "question_tokens": ["My", "God", ",", "this", "does", "n't", "get", "any", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I'm Jennifer's little monster.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "Jennifer", "'s", "little", "monster", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Maybe, Jennifer, you could explain to me why Harvey's a rascal?", "question_tokens": ["Maybe", ",", "Jennifer", ",", "you", "could", "explain", "to", "me", "why", "Harvey", "'s", "a", "rascal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer", "Harvey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Oh, God, what are these pictures?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "God", ",", "what", "are", "these", "pictures", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "You and nincompoop.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "and", "nincompoop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "In terms of acting, who are your great inspirations?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "acting", ",", "who", "are", "your", "great", "inspirations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Well, Meryl Streep, obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Meryl", "Streep", ",", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Can you get past Bradley's good looks?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "get", "past", "Bradley", "'s", "good", "looks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bradley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "JJR", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "How does it work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "He gave me tips once of -- on trying to stand my ground more and try to be like, no I want this.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "gave", "me", "tips", "once", "of", "--", "on", "trying", "to", "stand", "my", "ground", "more", "and", "try", "to", "be", "like", ",", "no", "I", "want", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Who do you think, David, is, pound for pound, the best actor in the world right now?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", ",", "David", ",", "is", ",", "pound", "for", "pound", ",", "the", "best", "actor", "in", "the", "world", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "That's a horrible question to ask a director.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "horrible", "question", "to", "ask", "a", "director", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "That's like choosing your favorite baby?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "like", "choosing", "your", "favorite", "baby", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "That's like asking your favorite baby.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "like", "asking", "your", "favorite", "baby", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "You're talking about actors and actresses?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "talking", "about", "actors", "and", "actresses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "Yes, I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Every girl loves a British accent.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "girl", "loves", "a", "British", "accent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Isn't that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "I also love England.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "also", "love", "England", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "You've spent a lot of time there, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "spent", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "there", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "Yes, I have.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "You eat fish and chips?", "question_tokens": ["You", "eat", "fish", "and", "chips", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]